Monroe, Don Morgan, how you doing, man?
What's going on? Hey, how would you feel
about being a panther, man? Amazing.
Amazing, actually.
>> [applause]
>> Hey, we're we're excited to have you,
man. Super excited.
>> [applause]
>> Hell of a player, man. We're jacked
We're jacked to get you. I'm going to
hand you off to our owner, David Tepper,
okay? All right. All right. Sounds good.
Sounds good. Congrats, man.
Hey
Hey, Monroe, you're doing good? You're
doing good? Yeah, I'm doing great. I'm
doing really good.
>> Well, you sound You sound happy, so
that's a good thing.
I'm feeling so good. Really good. No,
that's that's great. Hey, welcome
welcome into the welcome into the
Panther family, okay? [laughter]
Y'all keeping me in state, man.
All right. All right, I'm going to get
I'm going to hand you over to the coach
right here, okay? All right. Sounds
good.
>> Monroe, what's up, man?
What's going on? Oh, brother, this is a
great day. I'm glad it played out this
way. We're so fired up to get you here,
man. Oh, I'm so I'm so fired up, man.
We're going to
We're going to have to teach you what
keep pounding means, though, okay? So,
uh we'll get we'll get you initiated on
all that. I'm glad I'm glad you didn't
hold that against me.
Well, awesome. Hey, have fun. Enjoy this
time with your this moment with your
family and your friends.
I will. I will. I will.
All right, brother.
All right. Love you.
>> [laughter]
>> Love you, too. Congrats, man.
>> [applause]
[music]